momgiveaways.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Best Handheld Vacuum

BestHandheldVacuum.com (the “Website”) is committed to protecting your privacy to give you a safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your personal information

The Website collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, or telephone number. The Website also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your geographic location, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the Website. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by the Website to maintain quality content, services, products, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Website’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: the Website does not read any of your private online communications.

The Website encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to visit that are linked from the Website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The Website is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Website and the Website’s family of sites.

## Use of your personal information

The Website collects and uses your personal information to operate the Website and deliver the content, services, or products you have requested. The Website also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other content, products, or services available from the Website and its affiliates. The Website may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current (or potential new) content, services, or products.

The Website may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In addition, the Website may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All third parties are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Website does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

The Website keeps track of the pages our users visit within the Website or the Website’s family of sites, in order to determine what content, services, or products are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the Website to users whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

The Website or the Website’s family of sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the Website; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Website, or the public.

## Use of cookies

The Website uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the Website pages, or register with the Website or services, a cookie helps the Website to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Website features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Website services or pages you visit.

This site uses Google Analytics remarketing codes and logs when users view specific pages or take specific actions on this website. This will allow the Website to provide customized advertisements across the internet based on your specific interests. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to the Website. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertisement from us in the future you can opt out using the [opt-out form provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

## Security of your personal information

The Website secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Website secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Changes to this statement

The Website will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and user feedback. The Website encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how the Website is protecting your information.

## Contact information

The Website welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that the Website has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us using this [contact form](https://www.besthandheldvacuum.com/privacy-policy/#). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
